(Wil:)I was trying to save your life.
(Penny:)Life? What life?
Look at me! I'm a monster!
(Penny:)And now I have blood on my hands,
or paws. I don't know.
(Wil:)You can't give up.
I love you.
(Penny:)I love you too.
(Penny:)But I'm afraid I love killing more.
(Penny:)Like, one day,
I might actually try and kill you!
(Director:)And... cut.
All right.
(Raj:)All right,
let's set up for the next scene.
Actually, know what?
Can we do one more?
(Penny:)I think I could do it better.
(Director:)Let's just move on.
No one cares.
(Penny:)Well, I care.
I mean, look, if we're gonna do this,
(Penny:)why not try and make it
something we're actually proud of?
(Director:)Look, sweetie, this movie is garbage,
but you should be happy about that,
(Director:)'cause if it was a good movie,
you wouldn't be in it.
(Leonard:)Whoa, whoa, hang on.
There's no need to insult her.